<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_title">Sobre</string>

    <string name="about_title_dev">Developer</string>
    <string name="about_author_dev">AlphaDelete</string>
    <string name="about_content_dev">
        If you have any questions, feedback, comments or suggestions, please get in touch:

        \n\nhttp://www.twitter.com/alphadelete
        \n\nalphadelete@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="about_title_soft">Use and guarantee</string>
    <string name="about_author_soft">Água Consciente - Copyright 2015</string>
    <string name="about_content_soft">
        The calculations are approximate figures based on the information below and should be used for informational
        purposes only. The developer is not responsible for differences between the data collected and the actual
        consumption.

        \n\nThe initial data of this software are information provided by SABESP.

        \n\nBrushing teeth
        \n\nIf a person brushes his teeth in 5 minutes with not much water running, will be spent 12 liters of water.
        However, if wet the brush and turn off the tap while brushing your teeth and also rinse your mouth with a
        glass of water, can save more than 11.5 liters of water.
        (2.4 liters per minute in the worst case).
        \n\nWashing dishes
        \n\nIn a house, washing dishes with the water running through in 15 minutes, are used 117 liters of water.
        With economy consumption can reach 20 liters.
        (7,8 liters per minute per minute in the worst case).
        \n\nWashing clothes
        \n\nUsing an tank, with the valve open for 15 minutes, the spent water can reach to 279 liters.
        The best is to accumulate clothes, put the water in the tank to lather and keep the tap closed.
        (18 liters per minute in the worst case).
        \n\nBath time
        \n\nFor 15 minutes shower bath with the valve half open, consumes 135 liters of water.
        If we close the valve, while you lather, and reduce the time to 5 minutes, consumption drops to 45 liters.
        (9 liters per minute in the worst case).

        \n\nSource: http://site.sabesp.com.br/site/interna/Default.aspx?secaoId=140
    </string>
</resources>